欢迎回来。在本课程中，你将踏上激动人心的学习之旅，探索 chatGPT 的世界。
Welcome back. In this course, you'll be embarking on an exciting learning journey, exploring the world of  chatGPT.
我们将首先在人工智能、语言模型和 chatGPT 的巨大潜力方面打下坚实的基础。随着我们的前进，你将了解 chatGPT 的细节并通过实践练习进行练习，掌握提示工程的艺术以释放其全部潜力。
We'll start by building a strong foundation in AI, language models and the incredible potential of  chatGPT. As we move forward, you learn the ins and outs of  chatGPT and practice with hands-on exercises, mastering the art of prompt engineering to unlock its full potential.
然后，你将运用你的技能来创建从博客文章到广告文案的各种内容，并使用 chatGPT 进行高效的研究和信息收集。探索其在个人和职业发展中的作用，你将发现 chatGPT 如何简化工作流程和自动化任务。
You'll then apply your skills to create a variety of content from blog posts to ad copy and use  chatGPT for efficient research and information gathering. Exploring its role in personal and professional growth, you'll discover how  chatGPT can streamline workflows and automate tasks.
然后深入数字营销策略和分析的世界，我们将研究 chatGPT 对这些领域的影响，然后再将其用于工作申请、面试和社交。我们还将了解教育、编码和个人生活中的各种应用。
And then diving into the world of digital marketing strategies and analytics, we'll examine  chatGPT's impact on these areas before leveraging it for job applications, interviews and networking. We'll also learn about diverse applications in education, coding and personal life.
在本课程中，我们将使用行业特定示例来了解 chatGPT 如何应用于不同领域。最后，以下是 Udemy 上最重要的九个功能，可帮助你最大限度地提高学习效果。
Throughout this course, we'll be using industry specific examples to understand how  chatGPT can be applied across different fields. And finally, here are the nine most important functions on Udemy to maximize your learning.
第一，课程资源。你可以通过单击讲座并选择其中的相关材料来访问资源。
Number one, course resources. You can access resources by clicking on the lecture and selecting the relevant materials inside.
二、播放速率。使用播放器控件附近的播放速率按钮根据你的喜好调整视频速度。
Two, playback rate. Adjust the video speed to your preference by using the playback rate button that's near the player controls.
三、添加注释。要做笔记，请单击“添加笔记”并写下你的想法。
Three, add notes. To take notes, click add notes and write down your thoughts.
四、文字记录和说明文字。自动生成的文字记录可在文字记录选项卡下找到，而字幕可以通过单击字幕并将其打开来激活。
Four, transcripts and captions. Auto-generated transcripts are available under the transcripts tab, while captions can be activated by clicking captions and turning them on.
请注意，成绩单可能并不总是 100% 准确。五、问答。
Do note that transcripts may not always be 100% accurate. Five, Q&A.
如果你需要任何帮助，请单击“问答”按钮，向下滚动并搜索你的问题。或者问一个新的。
If you need any help, click the Q&A button, scroll down and search for your question. Or ask a new one.
我们的团队将在工作日 24 小时内回复。 6.
Our team will respond within 24 hours on weekdays. 6.
笔记。在这里找到所有关于特定时间戳的书面笔记。
Notes. Find all your written notes on their specific timestamps here.
7. 公告。
7. Announcements.
我们不断更新课程，你将完全免费收到这些更新。你可以在公告部分找到它们。
We continuously update the course and you'll receive these updates completely for free. You'll find them in the announcement section.
八、学习工具。设置提醒以对你的学习负责。
Eight, learning tools. Set reminders to stay accountable with your learning.
创建一个活动并决定你的频率。请记住，一致性是关键。
Create an event and decide on your frequency. Remember, consistency is key.
最后，九，课程完成。完成整个课程后，你将解锁奖杯符号，获得你的文凭，作为你在本课程中进行广泛培训的证明。
And finally, nine, course completion. After finishing the entire course, you'll unlock the trophy symbol, granting access to your diploma as a proof of your extensive training in this course.
现在你已经知道如何从本课程中获得最大收益，让我们继续下一讲。
So now that you know how to get the most out of this course, let's move on to the next lecture.